你觉得怎么样呢  他们准备好了吗
What do you think? They ready?
已经是他们的最佳状态了
As ready as they're ever gonna be.
过去的事情都一笔勾销  对吗
Slate is clean. Okay?
你什么也不欠我了
You owe me nothing.
你他妈是认真的吗
Are you fuckin' serious?
前情提 要
巴里
我在课上表演的角色
This piece that I'm doing for class,
不是凭空塑造的  就是真实的我
it's not a character. It's me.
如果我错了呢
What if I get it wrong?
整个地方都可以供你使用
The whole place is yours.
伙计们  既然我们马上就都要死了
Hey guys, since we're all about to die,
我得跟你们坦白
I have to be honest about something.
我很友好  很有礼貌
I'm nice. Polite.
我天生就是个乐观的人
I'm optometrist by nature.
是因为我刚刚在车上说的话吗
Guys. Is this about what I said on bus?
我刚刚是在励志
Because... I was delegating.
我要去一趟我的小屋
I'm headed up to my cabin.
有个私家侦探联系我
This private detective approached me.
-巴里  -啊
- Barry. - Ah.
我是吉恩·库西诺
My name is Gene Cousineau.
是我杀了珍妮丝·莫斯警探
I killed Detective Janice Moss.
巴里
第二季第 八 集(本季终)
坐下
Sit down.
Sit down!
所以  你和这个古雷说过话
So, you talked to this Goulet character?
是的
Yes.
你在树林里的时候
And while you were in the woods,
是听到警笛声  才找到那辆车的吗
you heard the sirens that brought you to the car?
是的
Yes.
我们在树林里搜索了一个月
The car that we couldn't find even after
也没有找到的那辆车
scouring the woods for a month?
库西诺先生还好吗
Is Mr. Cousineau okay?
你知道我第一次见到你时的想法吗
You know what I thought the first time I met you?
我想  巴里这个人真的很关心他的老师
I thought, wow, this Barry guy really cares about his teacher.
你几乎  是在保护他
You were almost... protective of him.
古雷这个人不是我们凭空捏造的
We're not making this Goulet guy up.
我很想相信你
I want to believe you.
因为在案件调查中  对警官撒谎是犯罪
Because lying to a police officer during an investigation is a crime.
但是  没有证据表明
But... there's no evidence to suggest
除了你和你的老师  树林里还有其他人
that anyone was up in the woods with you other than your teacher.
好了  你可以走了
Okay. You're free to go.
我能见一下库西诺先生吗
Can I see Mr. Cousineau?
不行  我们认为他杀害了他的女朋友
Oh, no. We think he killed his girlfriend,
所以他得待在这里
so he's staying here with us.
没错  这里是康特尔工业公司
Yeah, you've reached Comtel Industries.
要不你先留个言吧
Why don't you go ahead and leave a message.
福克斯
Fuches...
我来找你了
I'm coming for you.
你他妈的死定了
You're a fucking dead man.
欢迎大家来到你们的新家
I would like to welcome you guys to your new home!
虽然是我的功劳  但是不用客气啦
Which I got for you. You're welcome.
这个地方棒极了有没有
Oh, this place is great, isn't it?
就跟龙争虎斗里的一样  我说的对吧
It's like Enter Dragon. Am I right?
不过  我得把这玩意处理掉
Wow, need to get rid of this, though.
看着真是碍眼  要这破玩意干啥用
I mean, what an eyesore. What is that for even?
不管怎样  五小时内海洛因就会运到这
Anyway, heroin gets here in T-minus five hours.
所以  我们  伙计们
So, we're-- Guys?
知道我们需要什么吗
Hey! Know what we need?
放海洛因的桌子
Um, table to put the heroin on.
妈的  我这主意绝了
Fuck, that is such a great idea.
我要买一个  就放在这里
I'm going to buy one, put it right here.
海洛因桌  绝对酷毙了
Heroin table, that's got to be a thing, right?
我现在正在你们的网站上看呢
So, I'm on your website right now.
顺便说一下  家具真漂亮
Beautiful furniture, by the way.
我看到有餐桌
And I'm seeing dining room tables,
还看到了咖啡桌
I'm seeing coffee tables,
但不知道怎么搜索我要的桌子
but not sure how to look for the table that I need.
不  是放海洛因的
No, it's for heroin.
大约30公斤左右吧
About 30 kilos, give or take.
我想要雕花的木头桌脚  桌面要石头的
What I'm thinking is carved wood, stone top.
最好是大理石
Marble maybe.
我要的是一个开放式的设计
What I'm dealing with is an open floor plan,
所以它必须要能体现自己的价值
so it really needs to work on its own merit.
抱歉  你能等一下吗
I'm sorry. Can you hang on one minute?
谢谢
Thank you.
我是诺胡·汉克
This is NoHo Hank.
我是巴蒂尔  我刚刚下飞机
It's Batir. I just landed.
巴蒂尔  呃
Batir, uh...
你来加州了吗
you're here in California?
我是来接替你的  汉克
I've come to replace you, Hank.
你该回车臣去了
You're going home to Chechnya.
这事还有商量的余地吗
Is this open for discussion?
没有  我已经在安大略机场了
No. I am at Ontario Airport.
我要乘机场快车去修道院
I am taking Super Shuttle to monastery.
他们同意先送我
They promised to drop me first.
30分钟就能到
They say 30 minutes.
我的人正在加固这个修道院
My guys are fortifying this monastery
预防跟玻利维亚和缅甸人发生大规模交火
for when Bolivians and Burmese show up to have massive firefight.
我甚至没有时间买个放海洛因的桌子
I don't even have time to order heroin table,
我在拼趣上看的  不是亚马逊
which is a thing on Pinterest but not on Amazon.
拼趣：美国热门图片分享社区
而且现在  巴蒂尔来了
And now, Batir is coming.
他是从安大略来的  大概要花九个小时
I mean, he's coming from Ontario, so it'll take him like nine hours--
汉克  别说了  我挂了
I can't have this conversation anymore, Hank.
我的那些手下  他们都听你的
My guys, they'll listen to you.
我需要你告诉他们我是值得信任的
I need you to tell them that I am to be trusted.
我要失去他们了
I'm losing them!
他们私底下都用怀疑的眼光看我
There is suspiciously low level of eye contact going on.
你要告诉他们我是最好的领导者
Uh, tell them I am best leader, you know.
咱俩可以掰个手腕什么的
We arm wrestle, maybe--
-试镜咋样  -还行
- How was your audition? - Oh. Uh, it was fine--
我就问问  不需要回答
I'm really just asking. I don't need an answer.
快点  我们正在排练中
Come on, we're in the middle of tech.
等等  这什么地方
Wait. What is this place?
你知道吉恩在哪儿吗  大家都找不到他
Do you have any idea where Gene is? No one can get a hold of him.
我觉得  他在他的小屋里
Oh, he's at his cabin, I think.
他  他会来的
He-He'll be here.
好了  演员们  如果你们不演这场戏
Okay, actors, if you're not in this scene,
就先坐下来
just take a seat in the house.
看看这些座位
Look at all the seats.
没错  林赛把票都卖光了
Yeah, Lindsay sold out the whole place.
她告诉大家这是一场多元化的展示
She told people it was a "diversity showcase,"
我觉得他们应该也是不敢不来
and I think they were afraid not to RSVP.
好了  各位
Okay, everyone,
我们从杰梅因的演讲开始
let's take it from the bottom of Jermaine's speech.
开始吧  各位  开始
Here we go, everyone. Here we go.
是的我知道  我准备把它放那  谢谢
Yeah, I know. I'm going to set it there. Thank you. Shh! Shh!
我的爸爸曾是我的偶像  然后他消失了
My dad was my hero, and then he disappeared.
我的妈妈告诉我  我再也见不到他
My ma used to tell me that the reason I never saw him again
是因为他被外星人绑架了
was because he got abducted by aliens.
我曾经认真地相信过
I actually believed that
直到有一天  我看到他神志恍惚
till the day I saw him strung out,
在一个酒馆外  讨要钱财
begging for money, outside of a liquor store.
他没有认出我
He didn't recognize me.
这是怎么了
That's crazy, uh...
所以  我给了他一些钱
Uh, so I gave him some money
然后再也没见过他
and never saw him again.
我不知道  他是活着  还是死了
I don't know if he's dead or alive,
但我希望他知道  无论他在何方
but I just hope he knows, wherever he is,
他依旧是我的偶像
that he's still my hero.
即使是外星人也无法将此夺走
Not even aliens could take that away from me.
非常好  非常有感染力
That's beautiful, powerful. Woo!
演得很棒  好了  我们感受到了
Great job. Okay, we got that.
下一个  尼克
Let's move on to Nick.
萨莎  清理下那块
Sasha, strike that.
听着巴里  我也曾紧张过  明白吗
Look, Barry, I was nervous too, okay?
但每个人都放下了比惨的那套
But everybody's dropped the competitive grief bullshit,
而献上诚恳真挚的杰作
and they're delivering honest and real work.
是我们激发了他们的灵感
I mean, look what we inspired!
尼克  下一幕是你的呕吐
Nick, your vomit scene is up next.
天呐  这地方还有楼座
Jesus, this place has a balcony.
是  这地方全他妈是座位  下一话题
Yes, there's a lot of fucking seats! Move on!
两小时后开门
Doors open in two hours,
我认为我们需要开始排练了
I think we should start rehearsing.
大点声  尼克  大点声
Louder, Nick, louder.
好  好  不好意思  不好意思
Okay, okay. Sorry, sorry.
我们找不到这家伙
We can't find this guy.
但我们有一段911报警电话的录音
But we have a recording of a 911 call
你在里面承认自己谋杀了莫斯警官
where you confess to Moss's murder
还威胁说要自杀
and threaten suicide.
那不是我
It wasn't me.
但电话是从你手机打的
But the call came from your phone,
听上去也是你的声音
and it sounds like you.
库西诺先生  你能看着我吗
Mr. Cousineau, can you look at me?
你现在处境很糟
Mm. You're in a bad place.
内疚和悔恨让你心烦意乱
The guilt and remorse is weighing on you.
我懂
I get it.
你知道我是怎么看的吗
You know what I think?
我认为是你打电话给你的学生巴里
I think you called your student, Barry,
让他跟你串供  来撇清你自己
to talk you out of it.
因为你不想经历这些
'Cause you didn't want to go through with it.
巴里和他说过话
Barry spoke to him.
我不想再听到这个叫古雷的家伙
I don't want to hear about this Goulet guy.
他不存在
He doesn't exist.
到底发生了什么
What happened?
吉恩  没关系的
Gene, it's okay.
没关系
It's okay.
你们吵架了吗
Did you fight?
她是不是威胁要离开你了
Did she threaten to leave you
而你无法接受拒绝
and you couldn't handle the rejection?
她是我一生的挚爱
She was the love of my life.
库西诺先生  请起立
Mr. Cousineau, please stand up.
我们将以谋杀珍妮丝·莫斯的罪名逮捕你
You're under arrest for the murder of Janice Moss.
很快你就会被安排送回洛杉矶
We'll arrange for a transport for you back to Los Angeles.
你将被带往拘留室
You'll be taken to a holding cell,
你可以有一个电话的名额
and you'll be given one phone call.
请起立
Stand up, please.
令人印象深刻
Impressive.
看起来你给自己武装了一支军队
Looks like you got yourself an army.
-福克斯  -而我需要一只军队
- Fuches? - And I need an army.
圣贝纳迪诺警察署
San Bernardino Sheriff's Department.
这里威尔逊副官
Deputy Wilson speaking.
嗨  这里是巴里·波克曼
Hi. Yeah, this is, uh, Barry Berkman.
那个  你说过
Yeah? Uh, you said
如果有关于库西诺先生的新情况
I could call you,
我可以打电话给你
uh, with any updates on Mr. Cousineau.
我说的是  有新情况  我会打给你
I said I'd call you with any updates.
好了  同学们  两分钟后表演开始
Okay, guys, this show starts in two minutes.
-他怎么样  -已经收押了
- Well, how's he doing? - They just booked him.
你可以试着明天去洛杉矶警署看他
You can try to see him in LA County tomorrow.
-今晚就转移  -已经  收押了吗
- They are moving him tonight. - They-- they booked him?
是的
Yeah.
那  他还  还好吗
Well, is-is, uh... is he okay?
明天去看看他  波克曼
See him tomorrow, Berkman.
收到  我们会做的
Copy that. We'll get on it.
是的  我觉得"焦虑"
Yeah, I think "fraught" is
也许是我在寻找的词语
maybe the word I'm looking for.
是是  那不是我要
Yeah, that's not what I'm trying... Oh!
-我要  -好  请去吧
- Just, I got to... - Yeah. Oh, please.
-你好呀  兄弟  -操你大爷
- Hey, bud! - Fuck you!
其实
You know...
你完全可以救下你亲爱的老师
you could save your little acting teacher.
你知道的  对吗
You know that, right?
我会弄死你的  福克斯
I'm going to fucking kill you, Fuches.
你只要自首就可以了
All you have to do is turn yourself in.
为了他承认自己的罪行
Give it all up for him.
不是吗
Yeah?
现在不搞利他主义了是吧  小逼样的
Not so altruistic now, are you, motherfucker?
现在是谁没招了  再见吧您呐
Now who's out of moves? Buh-bye.
大家  都过来  都过来
Hey, everybody, bring it in. Bring it in. Woo!
库西诺团队加油
And...Go... Cousineau!
好的  所有人就位  就位  就位
All right, places everyone. Places, places.
-好戏登场  -嘿  你好  -你好
- Showtime! - Hey. Hi! - Hi.
好戏登场  如何  你还好吗
Showtime. Yeah. You feelin' good?
-挺好  应该没问题  -很好
- Yeah. Yeah. I think so. Yeah. - Good.
大家都来了  座无虚席
So everyone showed. The audience is packed.
每个人都来了  迈克兄弟也来了
Everyone is here. Oh, the Mikes are here.
那就是说他们同意这场演出计划吗
Oh, so they got on board with the whole showcase idea?
是啊  他们点头了  不过
Oh yeah, they're in, but...
他们还不知道  他们
They don't know. They're...
他们再怎么同意也就是这样了
They're as on board as they'll ever be.
也就是挺同意的
Which is pretty on board.
-我不是  你懂的  -别有压力
-I'm not-- I mean, you know... -No pressure.
完全没有压力  一定会
No pressure, exactly. It's going to be...
所以  嗯
So, um...
你觉得我们这么做是好的  对吧
You feel good that we're doing this, though, right?
我吗  我觉得非常好
Oh, me? I feel great that we're doing this!
我感觉很好  因为不管怎么说
I feel so good, because, at the end of the day,
你在讲述你的故事
you are telling your story.
你就是艺术家  而我在支持艺术家
You're the artist. I'm supporting the artist.
我把这些人带过来  因为这是你想做的
I brought all these people here because this is what you want to do.
你一定会很棒的  我相信你
And you're going to be great, and I believe in you.
这不就是我们开始做这件事的原因吗
Which is why we started this whole frickin' thing.
所以  我很兴奋  你很兴奋
So, I'm excited. You're excited.
萨利  你一定会很棒的  祝你好运
You're going to be great, and break a frickin' leg, Sally.
好的  回头见
Okay, see you later.
尼克  尼克  到你了  我们走
Nick, Nick, you're up, let's go.
她的合同可不能有这些吧
This is not what her contract was supposed to say.
这都不是正确的细节
These aren't the right details.
萨利是最后一个  所以你们得有耐心
Sally's is last, so you guys are going to have to be patient.
你知道马桶里有什么吗
You know what was in the toilet?
不是呕吐物
It wasn't the vomit,
或者是我放了三天  洒了漂白剂
or the three-day old pizza I poured bleach on
还是吃了的比萨饼
and still ate,
亦或是我瞎编的胃病
or even my made-up stomach issue.
是我
It was me.
It was me!
被遗忘
Forgotten.
被记起
Remembered.
又被遗忘
Forgotten.
我是四个拾来的孩子中最小的
I was the youngest of four gotten.
被遗忘掉
Forgotten.
四到拾  九  八  七  六
Four got ten, nine, eight, seven, six!
是我被抛弃在旧货市场的年纪
Was the age when I was left at a garage sale.
老天爷啊  汉克
I mean, Jesus, Hank.
-他们都在往这儿赶吗  -对
- They're all headed here now? - Yes.
我现在最需要的是巴里
What I need more than anything right now is Barry.
他就像是车臣暴徒的解语花
He is like crazy Chechen goon-whisperer.
这可能有点棘手  汉克
That might be a bit tricky, Hank.
我们出了点小意外
We had a minor falling out.
拜托  你们就像弗莱特伍德麦克
Oh, come on, you guys are like Fleetwood Mac.
弗莱特伍德麦克 上世纪60年代末成立的英国软摇滚风格乐队
你们解散  又重组
You break up, you get back together again,
然后又能制作出一张很棒的专辑
and then you go out and make a great album,
《弗莱特伍德麦克精选集》 专辑名
弗莱特伍德麦克精选辑不就是吗
like The Best of Fleetwood Mac.
可能比那要更彻底一点
This may be more final than that.
所以我才来寻求你们的照应  不是吗
Which is why I need your guys to get my back, yes?
好吧  恐怕是为时已晚无力回天了
Yeah, well, day late and ruble short, I'm afraid.
他们根本不听我的  伙计
They won't listen to me, man.
但他们会听巴里的
But they will listen to Barry.
巴里有什么了不起的  是我造就了他
Barry? Come on. I'm the guy that made Barry!
他们该听我的
They'll listen to me.
嘿  伙计们  都过来
Hey, fellas! Come back here.
伙计们  伙计们
Guys. Guys!
倒霉
Shit.
我也在想
Also, I was thinking that--
福克斯
Fuches?
听好  伙计们  我们现在要打仗了
Okay, guys, we're going to be in a war now.
-我真为你们兴奋  -你好
- I'm so excited for you guys! - Hello!
看你带的枪支和人马的数量
You know, seems like you brought a lot of people and guns
不像是来进行友好交谈的
for a talk with friends.
这是谁
Who is this?
疯老头子
Viejito loco.
对  真悲哀
Yes. Muy triste.
他  他在和我们说话吗
Is... Is he talking to us?
不是  好像  不是  他在用蓝牙
No, maybe-- No, he's on the Bluetooth.
我看不  他在用蓝牙吗
I can't-- Is he on the Bluetooth?
克里斯托巴尔  伙计
Cristobal, buddy, wow!
哦  好了  我听到了我的名字
Oh. Okay. I hear my name.
他在和我们说话
He is talking to us.
这老头是谁啊
我看不下去了
I can't watch.
克里斯托巴尔  艾斯特
Cristobal. Esther.
见到你们真高兴
Nice to meet you.
知道吗  在美国  艾斯特是个女人名
You know, in America Esther's a woman's name.
你他妈的是谁
Who the fuck are you?
福克斯  门罗·福克斯
Fuches. Monroe Fuches.
我是  汉克的代表
I'm, uh, Hank's representative.
说正事
Let's get to it.
你们是来杀我们的
You came here to kill us.
好吧  谋杀
Okay. Murder.
我以前认为像你这样的人就是狗屎
I used to think people like you were the shit, man.
像你这样的坏蛋总是让我很惊异
Bad-asses like yourself always fascinated me.
可是  真正做起来
But-But doing it, you know,
真正地去扣动扳机  结束生命
actually pulling the trigger, ending a life...
得是没有灵魂的人才能做到
Well, that takes someone with no soul.
汉克想暗算我
Hank tried to criss-cross me.
你和汉克  你们处在过渡阶段
You and Hank, you're in a... transitional phase,
仅此而已
that's all.
你知道  人和人相遇  有时候
You know, people meet and sometimes...
就会互相锁定
they lock into each other
就像一直在寻找彼此的拼图块
like two long-sought-after pieces of a puzzle.
可是呢  随着时间的推移
Now, as time goes on,
这些碎片  它们会变形  它们会成长
these pieces, they morph and they-they grow.
他们可以一起成长  变得更强大
And they can grow together and become stronger.
或者…
Or...
它们会变成完全不同的两个形状
they can become two completely different shapes that...
不再给对方留下任何空间
they don't have any room for each other,
它们不再合适了
they don't fit anymore.
如果说我在生活中学到了什么的话
If there's one thing I've learned in my life,
那就是你无法控制别人要做什么
you can't control what other people are going to do.
完全不能
No. No.
他们需要自己的空间来
They need their own space to...
成长为自己希望的任何千奇百怪的鬼样子
become whatever weird-ass shape they're going to change into.
这就是天性  你是无法控制的  但是
It's nature. You can't control it, but...
你可以选择接受
you can accept it.
并且我认为  就是
And I think, you know,
你和汉克  还是很合适的  兄弟
you and Hank, that's still a fit, man.
我真的很抱歉  兄弟
I'm so sorry, man.
你在逗我吗
Are you kidding me?
你在跟我开玩笑吗
我曾经想要杀了你的  兄弟
I tried to screw you over, man.
不是的  你只是想要杀了艾斯特
No, you only tried to kill Esther
因为你非常在乎我
because you cared about me.
听着  我爱你  好吗
Look, I love you, okay?
这次说了以后还算数吗
Can we just say that once and for all?
听着  我爱你  兄弟
Look, I love you, man.
我就是觉得
And I just think,
现在海洛因什么的都运来了
with the heroin shipment coming in and everything,
你明白吗
you know...
我们现在坐拥一个金矿了
...we're sitting on a gold mine!
你是我的心  我亲爱的小宝贝
Te llamo mi corazon . My little papita .
老天爷  要这么基情四射吗
Jesus Christ, easy, easy.
你们就像是我养的猫一样
You guys are like my cats.
我还得呲水才能把你们分开
I have to pour water on you.
来吧  让我们庆祝一下
Come on! Let's celebrate.
我们可以派人去拉尔夫家  买点三明治
We can send somebody to Ralph's, get sandwiches.
然后  再来点摇滚音乐
And, you know, case of Rolling Rock,
让我们嗨起来
let's do it up!
天啊  我出了好多汗
Ugh, I'm sweating.
好吧  你们显然没有听明白
All right, you guys clearly don't get this,
让我们总结一下
so to recap
这个
This...
走在这条街上
was walking down this...
被她看见了
and it was seen by her.
不  不是她  这不是我的照片
Not-- not actually her. This is not a photo of me.
我没有自己童年时候的照片
I don't have any photos of myself from my childhood
因为我的叔叔在我妈还在屋里时
because my uncle burnt down my house
把房子烧了
when my mum was still inside,
但是这个
but that's...
这件事和这个故事无关  对吗
that is not relevant to this story, is it?
好吧  林赛看起来真的很紧张
Okay, Lindsay seems really nervous.
万一这一幕没有成功呢
What if the scene doesn't work?
说出真相是正确的  对吗
Telling the truth is the right thing to do, right?
巴里
Barry?
说出真相是正确的  对吗
Telling the truth is the right thing to do, right?
巴里
Barry!
我的天啊  你还好吗
Oh my God, are you okay?
好了  该你们了  伙计们
Okay, it's time, guys.
祝你们演出成功
Break legs.
他妈的
Fuck.
巴里  你还好吗
Hey, Barry, are you okay?
说话啊  你还好吗
Come on. Are you okay?
他妈的
Fuck!
巴里  我们这样做是个好主意  对吗
Barry, it's a good idea we're doing this, right?
杰梅因  我是杰梅因
Jer-Jermaine. I am Jermaine.
你不认为这是个错误吧
You don't think this is a mistake?
把那个还给我
Give me that back.
试着呼吸就好了
Just try to breathe.
重点不是马
It's not horses.
我只是喜欢它们神奇的
It's just that I love their magical...
你神游到哪里去了
Hey, where are you at right now?
-我需要你精神集中  -我很集中
- I need you present. - I am present.
不  别这样  加油  集中注意力
No, come on. Come on. Focus.
加油  集中注意力  看着我
Come on, focus. Look at me.
我们就  我们练一下掐脖子  好吗
Let's just, let's practice the choke, ready?
什么
What?
掐脖子  准备好了吗  一  一二三
The choke. Ready? One-- one, two, three.
别这样  巴里  认真点
Come on, Barry, sell it!
我很认真
I am selling it.
保持好这个状态
Stay in that place.
谢谢你  萨莎
Sasha Thank you.
等等  我要拿上那个  我要拿上那个
Oh wait, I'm going to take that. I'm going to take that.
我要把那个带回家  我太喜欢了
I'm going to take that for my house. Love that!
秒杀全场
Oh, killed it.
那是
It was...
一个典型的十一月夜晚
It was a typical November night.
外边很冷
It was cold outside.
而且他喝酒了
And he had been drinking.
今天晚上跟你跳舞的那个男的是谁
Who was that guy you were dancing with tonight?
你是说肯吗
Ken?
他只是一个朋友  山姆
Well, he's just a friend, Sam.
我不喜欢这样  这很尴尬
I didn't like it. It was embarrassing.
你看起来像是一个臭婊子
You looked like a fuckin' whore.
别这样  山姆
Come on, Sam.
别  别像一个白痴
Don't-- Don't be an idiot.
别他妈的叫我白痴
Don't fucking call me an idiot!
我就叫你傻逼白痴
I'll call you a fucking idiot!
而且  你知道吗
Yeah, and you know what else?
我乐意跟谁说话  就他妈跟谁说话
I'll talk to who I please, when I please.
我不是你的附属品  你个死变态
You don't own me, you fucking prick!
而且从现在起  我要说出我的想法
And from now on, I'm going to speak my mind.
我想说什么就说什么  从这句开始
I'll say what I want to say, starting with this
我的名字是萨利·简·瑞德
My name is Sally Jane Reed,
而且从今天起
and, as of today,
我们结束了  你个狗娘养的
we are fucking done, you son of a bitch!
该死的
Shit...
这就是我们的全部演出
And that's our show...
萨利  等一下  等一下  你要去哪
Sally. Hey. Hey, hey! Where you going?
-发生什么事情了  -我需要离开这里
- What's going on? - I got to get out of here.
-没关系的  -不是的
- It's fine! - No.
告诉我  告诉我发生了什么
Tell me-- tell me what happened.
我只是  我不知道
I just, I don't know.
我看到那么多观众
I saw all those people,
然后  我就  我就慌了
and I just-- I kind of panicked.
所以我站在台上时  我说谎了
So, I got up there and I... I lied.
我说谎了  我不是一个艺术家
I actually lied. I'm not an artist.
你应该进去  你应该
You should go in there. You should be--
那也是真相的另一种形式
That's a different kind of truth.
我有点强迫你在别人面前暴露自己的内心
I was kind of forcing you to expose in front of everyone.
萨利  我真的非常抱歉
Sally, I just really want to apologize,
-变成这样我也很过意不去  -不
- because I feel very bad about this situation. - No, no...
我不该让你处于那样的境地
And I should not have put you in that position.
你不该被逼着
You should never have had to do
在这么短时间内
something so incredibly vulnerable
-在众人面前做这么心碎的事  -萨利
- in front of so many people with so little time. - Sally.
我原本完全没料到你会有这样的表现
So that was not at all what I thought you were going to do.
现在我们知道
And now we know why
你为什么恨亚伦·莱恩的故事了
you hated Aaron Ryan's story so much.
他的故事黑暗  真实  而且说真的
His story was dark and gritty and, frankly,
是讲困于无望境地的女人们的
kind of a bummer about women
令人无比厌恶的故事
who get trapped in a hopeless existence.
但你的故事充满希望与救赎
But yours was full of hope and redemption
讲述了一个掌控自己的生活的女人
about a woman taking charge of her life.
真的很发人深省
Really inspiring.
不像其他的人那些故事  真的很丧
And not like those other stories which were a bummer.
我还挺喜欢马的那个
I liked the one about the horse.
还有你演说的方式
And the way you did that speech.
那就像  《勇敢的心》
It was like... Braveheart.
《勇敢的心》：1995年美国电影  华莱士刑前高唤自由的场景十分出名
《勇敢的心》  没错
Braveheart, exactly.
就是这种破烂玩意儿让我
Look this is exactly the kind of fucking shit that I--
打扰一下  瑞德小姐
Excuse me, Ms. Reed?
我丈夫和我都觉得你演得很棒
My husband and I thought you were amazing.
她在这儿呢  太惊人了
There she is. That was breathtaking.
我有个朋友有类似的经历
I have a friend who went through a similar situation.
她没有勇气做你刚刚做的事
She did not have the courage to do what you just did.
真的很激励人
Truly inspiring.
-她哭了  -我在哭  真的一直在哭
- She was crying. - I was crying. I was really crying.
你就在这儿上回洛杉矶的车吧
Your ride back to LA is here.
你就在洛杉矶见律师  接受传讯
You'll meet your lawyer and be arraigned in Los Angeles.
等等
Hold on.
梅  你得进来一下
Mae, you need to come in here.
失陪一下
Excuse me.
好了  库西诺先生
Okay, Mr. Cousineau.
库西诺先生
Mr. Cousineau?
你可以回去了
You're free to go.
他可以走了
He's free to go.
我是查德·威尔逊警官
This is Officer Chad Wilson
这里是圣贝纳迪诺警局
of the San Bernardino Sheriff's Department...
喂
Hello?
你好
库西诺先生在吗
Uh, is Mr. Cousineau there?
请问您是
Uh, who is this?
我是巴里·布洛克
Uh, this is Barry Block.
您是
Who's this?
我  我是里奥
I'm-- I'm Leo.
我是  他的儿子
I'm his-- his son.
你好  他还好吗
Hi, um, is he okay?
他们把他送去洛杉矶了吗
Have they taken him to LA yet?
不  事实上  他们放他走了
No, actually, they're letting him go.
我才刚到  所以
I just got here, so...
他们放他走了  怎么回事
They're letting him go? What happened?
我猜他们是在珍妮丝的后备箱发现了什么
I-- I guess they found this thing in Janice's trunk.
是车臣胸章
It's a Chechen pin.
意思是  "债已还清"吗
So this translates to "The debt has been paid"?
我们的人是这么翻译的
That's what our guy is telling us.
他们把东西丢在那儿  就是希望我们
They must have left it there as a message
找到她尸体的时候能接收到这个信息
for when we found her.
是车臣人干的
Chechens did this.
那好
Oh, good, uh...
你能跟我保持联系吗
Can you keep in contact with me?
他没事的话就告诉我
Just to let me know he's okay?
行啊  我
Uh, sure, I--
你刚刚说你叫巴里·布洛克吗
Barry Block? Is that what you said?
是波克曼
It's Berkman.
我叫巴里·波克曼
My name's Barry Berkman.
行  好  我到时候跟你说
Okay, yeah, I'll let you know.
还有  你能帮我跟你爸说点事吗
Well, and-- and can you tell your dad something for me?
可以啊
Uh, sure.
能拜托你告诉他  他会没事的  还有
Can you tell him that he's going to be okay and that, uh...
他是对的
and that he was right?
我很确定  人是会变的
I'm pretty sure that people can change.
好  我跟他说
Okay. Will do.
诺胡·汉克
别担心问题解决了
福克斯在这儿
白人男性  露露柠檬运动装
White boy. Lululemon track suit.
巴里
Barry?
操
Shit!
-福克斯  -不
- Fuches! - No!
福克斯
Fuches!
妈的  操蛋
Oh shit! Shit!
操
Aw, fuck!
伙计们  让我进去
Guys! Let me in!
干  妈的
Ow! Yes!
救我
Help me!
你  你们
Oh! You, you.
把我藏起来  他要杀我  他要来杀我
Hide me, he's trying to kill me. He's trying to kill me!
这样  你想要什么我都给你
I'll tell you what, I'll give you anything you want!
赶快把我弄出去
Just get me the fuck out of here!
弗拉德  巴里的师父
Vlad, Barry's mentor.
-他师父  -让我出去  让我出去
- His mentor? - Get me out. Get me out.
巴里的师父
Barry's mentor!
你们把他藏那儿了吗
Hey! Hide him in there?
他在里面  他是不是在里面
Is he in there? Is he in there? Hey!
妈逼的  你妈逼的破门
Motherfuck... Motherfuckin' door!
操你妈的
Fucking...
他在哪儿  他人在哪儿
Where is he? Where is he!
福克斯
Fuches!
福克斯  你个狗娘养的
Fuches, you fuck!
福克斯
Fuches!
操
Fuck!
巴蒂尔
Hey, Batir!
你好呀  兄弟
Hey, man!
爸  要喝点茶吗
You, um, you want some tea, Dad?
巴里·波克曼杀的
Barry Berkman did this.
我的天
Oh, my God!